NO, THEY ARE ACTUALLY, AS WE
SPEAK, TRYING TO OVERTHROW THE
CORE LAW ENFORCEMENT FUNCTION OF
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
OF COURSE, THIS IS, I THINK,
WHAT WE'RE TALKING PAST EACH
OTHER.
WHEN ICE OFFICERS HAVE TO STREET
BATTLE AGAINST ANTIFA, HAND-TO-
HAND COMBAT EVERY NIGHT TO COME
AND GO FROM THEIR BUILDING, WHEN
THEY TRY TO EXIT IN A VEHICLE,
WHEN THEY ARE SWARMED AND
SURROUNDED AND THEY TRY TO TIP
THE VEHICLE OVER, WHEN PEOPLE
TRY TO ENGAGE IN DIRECT VIOLENT
ASSAULT AGAINST ICE OFFICERS, WHAT
IS THE PURPOSE?
IT IS TO PREVENT IMMIGRATION AND
CUSTOMS ENFORCEMENT FROM CURRING
OUT THE MISSION THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE ELECTED THEM TO DO.
YOU MAKE THE CASE THAT THESE
ARE TERRORISTS, BUT IN WHAT WE'VE
SEEN THUS FAR, THE ACTUAL
INCIDENTS OF PEOPLE INCITING
VIOLENCE AND NOT RESPONDING TO
LAW ENFORCEMENT ATTEMPTING TO
DISBURSE THEM ARE NOT ALL
OPEN REBELLION.
I MEAN, AGAIN, YOU MAKE THIS
CHARACTERIZATION AS THOUGH
THEY'RE TERRORISTS, AND I DO
WONDER IF IT'S
STORM.
DONE THE MENTAL
STOP  SUBORES MEMBERS, THAT LEFT